welcome back
and as you can see on my back
we now have a lot of brick blast furnaces
and that did cause quite a lot of pollution
and that's precisely why I build those far from my house
um, maybe some people say I overdid it with all of those brick blast furnaces
but I kind of enjoyed building those
so many people like to do mob farms to get steel
but I don't like mob farms, magic stuff
I want to play a industrial game, technological game
and brick blast furnace is the way we go for a industrial technological game
but I mean, that's just my take
I even left those running a lot of AFK
so now I have so much steel I can do
too many steel
by the way, going in such polluted areas can give you quite some debuffs
if you don't want to deal with that
there is a quest that will trade some
there is a quest here that will trade a hazmat suite for some glue
some rubber
to give some rubber to the quest book
it will give you a hazmat suit
that armor will protect you from the pollution
but it has a really low durability
so you should only put this armor on when you go next to the polluted areas
anyways that we have plenty of steel
we can finally start working on the LV age
usually in the old versions, I would suggest making one stack of motors using those are recipes
because we are going to need a lot of motors
so crafting a lot at once
we make it so you have a lot of motors already
and you won't have to worry about crafting more
but nowadays that crafting motors is just that easy
I mean I don't have to manually craft this
manually craft that
and then manually craft those
I think it's just crafting those one at a time
when you need those is actually better
because the batch crafting was just so you wouldn't have to manually craft all of these steps
but now that NEI crafts everything in a single click in less than one second
it's probably more efficient to craft just only the stuff you need
so you don't waste materials with the less efficient recipes
and thus we crafted the basic things required to get into the LV age
we are going to need more or less all of those machines
but there are some that are more useful than others
for example, my suggestion is to start with a wire mill
which is one of the cheapest machines to build
and it will greatly increase the yield of wires
instead of getting two wires out of three ingots
you will get two wires out of one ingot
and now, it's time to connect those machines
there are a little bit of trouble you have to check
this pipe can only handle two of those turbines
but whatever
you can always do a little bit however you like
you have to know how it works
so you know if something works or not
I mean at the end of the day
if something doesn't work
just about it
I think the main thing you have to know
if you're not experience enough
and oftentimes is not stressed enough is that
this cable has a little bit of power loss
that means that every block the energy has to go through, a little bit of energy will be lost
so try to keep the energy intensive machines next to the generators
I did a video in the past where I better explain how it works
the wiremill can go there for now
and another trick is that if you make the cables with circuit sixteen
should be a little bit faster than doing it with the other one
this one is a sixteen x cable
it takes seventy seconds
so it's basically one second per wire wise
but if you do the normal wire
it takes five seconds for two
making a sixteen x cable is about twice as fast
and once you have the big cable
you can just
split manually into small cables
doing sixteen x small dimension
and finally, remember that you can automate a little bit
I wouldn't automate crafting chains
specially for now
specially with NEI auto crafting
but having at least an auto input on one side with an auto output on another side is probably helpful
that way you can just leave a lot of materials to process here for machine
and machine will leave the output in another chest
this is the kind of automation you probably want at this point of the game
next, if your machine stall due to lack of power
you can use a soft mallet toggle it off or on again
you can also use redstone to power machines
each redstone is worth one thousand EU
but I wouldn't use it
unless you are in some very very very specific situation
using redstone to power machine is not worth it
yeah, ideally you want to make sure that your turbines never run out of fuel
by the way, I'm using steam turbines
but there are many different ways of producing electricity
most people try to go with other fuel sources
I have my own mean way of playing
because I like playing this way
anyways, at this point there are many many many machines you probably want to get
probably you want to get everything the quest book shows as I said earlier
and you probably want to read every single quest that there is in this age
many of those things are quite useful
I think the most useful but probably not is the magnet
I really like to have a magnet to easily pick up all of the ore while digging
I just think it's so nice to not have to move around to pick up every single item that drops
by the way, to get the magnet and the lithium battery
and to get lithium
my suggestion is to get multiblock steams centrifuge
this one is way more efficient than an LV electric version
it has some discounts, it has parallel
and you don't have to deal with the inefficiency of these turbines
you can also use the centrifuge to get cobalt or gold
to get gold, here I did a mistake
if you want to get gold
there are multiple ways
you can figure it out in NEI
but my suggestion to get gold is to crush some copper
then wash it
turn off the magnet
wash it
you can see in NEI
if you wash it you get cobalt
if you use a washing machine you get the cobalt
if you use the cauldron you do not get the byproducts
same with the macerator
to get the byproduct of the macerator steps
to get those byproducts under the macerator
you need at least a HV macerator
which is two tiers ahead
so right now you can't get this by product for example
but to get gold easily
you can process the copper like this
so first you macerate it
then you wash it in a cauldron
I mean you could use a normal washing machine
but that machine once again is rather slow and annoying
there is a steam version multiblock
but I don't need that (by-product?) right now
so I'm simply going with this way
and then you throw it into the centrifuge
and that should give us gold after this dust is done
come on
OK, and I can get gold like that
same things apply to lithium
you can find this ore is rather easy to find and collect
centrifuge the impure dust and you get lithium
so to get this one, you do not wash it
you crush it without washing
by the way to get the lead
you have to make a quick and dirty portal generator to access the twilight forest
here you will find a vein made out of lead and silver
which you can use to make potin
which is one of the best materials for pipes
or at least at this tier
it's really really really good material for pipes
but most importantly
we can use the silver to get the high pressure solar boilers
which are my favorite way of generating energy
the main issue of those boilers is that
every now and then you have to break and remove the block if you do not want to lose two thirds of your steam production
and when you do so
those will take a lot of water to fill up
so, you better have a good system to make sure those never run out of water
especially when you replace the block
and with about twenty of those solar boilers
we can finally power the main objective of this age
the electric blast furnace
and the main challenge that this multiblock will pose is fueling it properly
this multiblock to run will need one hundred and twenty EU per tick
and as I showed earlier
those cables have a little bit of loss
you really don't have much margin for error in this situation
so the suggestion that is given is use two energy hatches
one piece of cable on each of the two energy hatches
do not connect those two
and then you put the turbines in a way that they connect directly to those cables
the thing is that each one of those energy hatches can accept two amps
and the machine itself needs four amps at thirty EU per tick
so here you have a loss of one
with one block you already get thirty one
if you lose one more
you have no margin
you are basically net gainer (?)
so if for some reason some packets of power are lost
in the multiblock will fail
you can also add a third energy hatch if you want
and that third energy hatch will provide extra power intake that is not used
and that could make up for power loss
I don't suggest using battery buffers here
but theoretically you could
but you still have the issue that you must ensure that the multiblock gets the one hundred and twenty EU per tick
if you use two energy hatches
must make it get super tight
you can add a third one for the loss
I would try to reduce as much as possible the power loss here
then some people at this age use benzene other fuel sources
I'm still using steam
to use steam
you have to be a little bit careful
because LV steam turbines require one thousand five hundred fifty two steam per second to run
so you must make sure you are providing that much steam
those are four
so we need about seven thousand steam per second
and the normal potin pipe is just six thousand
so I wouldn't risk using this one
I'd rather go with the large one
and there we go
we power the EBF
you also have to do maintenance
you can make a soldering alloy, soldering iron which is probably what I'm going to do
future, but
right now, I'm lazy
let's get the duct tape
loot bags are not that good, I mean
that is a single use item
so probably loot bags were better
but I'm lazy
so there we go
and by the way
if for whatever reason your multiblock loses its maintenance
will be prompt to do maintenance
OK here you can see
the tools required as are different things
so you can see the first one is a crowbar
second should be either soft
there are both the soft mallet and the hard hammer
screwdriver, soldering alloy and wrench
so you take those tools
and click with those tools inside the maintenance hatch
I click hatch, OK
but we don't have, OK
you can also click with those two things
I showed the duct tape earlier
now you can see the wrench is done
but the best thing is to just get a field engineer toolbox
but that thing requires some polyethylene
I was planning originally on keeping polyethylene for the next episode
but you know what
let's see some automation in LV
polyethylene is a long crafting chain
I mean it's not really that long if you know GTNH
but it's the first one you most likely want to do
there are many ways of going on to do that one
may get a little bit lost
the quest for polythene is actually in MV
but you can totally do it in LV
and I actually suggest doing in LV
both the silicon and the polythene quest lines
so, to make it, the first
there are many ways as I said
most likely, I suggest starting with oil
but before we actually go get oil
I think we want our blast furnace to start running
the soldering iron is the most annoying tool to craft
as every other tool
you can make it in many different ways
I just went with the steel bolt version, but
you can make it out of many different things
just use whatever battery and whatever bolt you have
the only thing is that every material has a different rod
I use a steel bolt with iron rod
I already crafted it without recording
this is an electric tool
so you have to charge it up
you can put it in any charging slot of a machine
and then you charge it up
you also need some soldering alloy in your inventory
which is made by allowing together tin with antimony
and then you just pass it through a wiremill to make the fine wire
and then once you have all of the tools
you just click this one
think I have to move the tools
if you don't have the toolbox
you have to manually click with each tool
to do the maintenance of the block
once again, you can either do that or later on we would get this one
which basically you put every tool inside this thing
and then you simply use this thing
or you just use the duct tape as I did earlier
and now it can run again
OK we got our blast furnace
we can use this one to make steel way faster
it can make steel in five seconds
unlike the six minutes of the brick version
it uses quite a lot of power
it should be way more power efficient
to make steel in the primitive brick blast furnace
you need four coal
while here you need twelve thousand EU
there is also oxygen
but the thing is that this boiler for example can make almost forty thousand steam with one coal
forty thousand steam is twenty thousand EU
one coal with this boiler will be able to make one and a half ingots
while here we need four coal
so, energy wise it's more efficient
I didn't account for the power losses
but more or less
it's why, it's at least
it's very going to be at least three times as sufficient
and it was this way faster
but the main reason we build this one anyways is not to get steel
but to get aluminum
to do so, we can either use seventy five seconds with a compressed aluminum dust
I'm not even sure how to get the pure aluminum dust nowadays
it used to be relatively easy to get pure aluminum dust back in the day
but I think nowadays you can't even get the aluminum dust anymore
this one probably doesn't work
probably in MV
once you start electrolyzing, you can get this one
the proper way of doing it is by mixing together alumina and cryolite
cryolite is an ore you can find in twilight forests
while alumina can be obtained out of a few things
i don't suggest it, but you can find a lot of sapphire in the twilight forest
and you can EBF the sapphires into alumina
but that's just one way
the biggest suggestion I'm going to give you for this tier
which this video probably going to be one of the lowest quality
I just follow the quest book
in this age, there are so many things you may want to do or don't
my biggest suggestion is just look around
figure out what you think you may like
try different things
I'm trying to show you the main things you should probably try to remember, I know
but I don't think just watching a video will help you too much
just try to play around and figure out things on your own
remember to look at every quest
and remember to look at every possible recipe in NEI
because there are many recipes
many ways of doing things
most recipes are recycling too
the modpack too keeps getting updates which keep changing things
in this age my biggest suggestion is
you have a huge waiting time for distill or other things
so use that waiting time to look around
and figure out how you can do things
and just with the aluminum by product of processing cryolite
we can now turn on our EBF
and that will take a little bit of time
but every new tier we will have a material that will take a little bit to process
as usual, use this time to figure out what else you can do
or just build more of that machine
this run I'm going to chill out
so I'm just going to leave the game AFK until we have a lot of aluminum
and after a little bit of waiting
we got enough aluminum to get (?) two MV machines
two MV machines
the electrolyzer
actually OK
with this one
I can get an MV electrolyzer
and the MV electrolyzer will making aluminum production way easier
because theoretically
we can just electrolyze amount of clay to get all of the aluminum we could possibly need
one of the main ways I usually get aluminum is that
yes, get to MV because you need MV for that recipe
lazurite, this is an ore that you get in huge amounts
one ore makes twelve
so you can get a lot of this
and this one gives a lot of silicon, sodium, aluminum calcium, all good stuff
but the main way, oh wait
did they change, oh, wait
don't suggest to be like the meta
not really the meta but
oh yeah this one
don't know why I couldn't find it
this is a really nice recipe
if you find a Canyon biome
set up a little bit of automation
where you tunnel the world Canyon biome through all of the clay into a macerator
and then electrolyze to get a huge load of those things
sodium can be burned, wait can it?
oh yeah, you can burn the sodium in a boiler
I think they nerf it
I remember this one burning more
but most likely you want to use the sodium for other stuff
you can make some decent batteries if you want to use a battery buffer later with sodium
lithium is great for batteries
don't burn it
and then you get the aluminum
you get aluminum
these are the receipt used to yield five aluminum, I think
so yeah, OK, nowadays this is trash for producing aluminum
it used to be a way
it was also a little bit of manual work collecting all of the clay
but I think nowadays this is no longer the way of doing it
I'm going to figure out another way of getting aluminum I guess
anyways, the other thing you want out of your EBF to progress in MV is some gallium arsenide
you can get your arsenic in different ways
once again, check the quest book
I got it out of centrifuging the realgar
but that's kind of uh
like I had the realgar so I just went with it
it's a small ore that you can find in nether
this one spawns as a small ore in the nether
just random ores
while you collect other materials
you probably get a few of these
you can centrifuge it
probably going to be enough
and then for the gallium you use sphalerite
here I'm processing sphalerite like that because I do need the gallium
should be, let's check if they changed it too, yeah
you electrolyze this sphalerite
you have nine percent chance of getting gallium
but if we had an HV macerator
we could get way more gallium out of sphalerite
there are also other ways
the sphalerite is also used in something we will see way later
so, I would like to say don't process or you don't need processed
because in the future this ore would be quite useful
but I'm also thinking by the time we need this one for this thing which we we eventually see
at that time, we will have some huge multiblock drilling rigs
that will get us just so much of this ore
that whatever we save at this tier will be meaningless compared to what we will be able to get in that age
also, I'm not going to make you a list
of course you do not want to process
it doesn't make any sense to play like that
I had the tendency of saving those materials
because I already know how it's going to be
but if you don't really know those things
don't even try to look into it
and after a way too unlucky run
we've finally got our gallium dust
which we can throw into the furnace with circuit two
to make gallium arsenide, perfect
the quest book wants you to use it
to macerate it
to make diode
but once again
the quest book suggests you to do this recipe which gets you two diodes out of ...
I think sixteen diodes out of the one gallium arsenide once you macerate it into small dust
but if you use polythene
you get twice as much
and if you go one step ahead and make the wafers
those are required silicon
you are going to get like many more
because this wafer you get sixteen out of one boule
one boule cost a quarter of a gallium arsenide
so it's way more efficient if you try to do this a recipe here instead
which also require the polyethylene and the silicon which I mention earlier and
while we wait
while we wait for things
like you can either just use the better recipe
collect a little bit more sphalerite
process the arsenic out of cobaltite
and then just go with that
or you can just make the two setups I mentioned earlier
now, as I said so many times starting this video
usually get silicon and polyethylene in LV
so can do that
but the thing is that right now to power machines
I'm putting steam machines everywhere
many people, too many people in my opinion
like to spam generators
like they even added the
they even added an IV gas turbine
many people like to have a main fuel line
make a pipe with some energy dense fluid
like if you use diesel or benzine
a super tiny pipe can fuel very powerful hungry machines
if you use steam
you need huge pipes
but the thing I don't like is having all of those pipes with all of those generators
feel like the generators are look not that expensive to craft
but I just don't like that play style
I'd rather centralize energy earlier
usually I centralize energy in HV
but in this run I think I'm going to try to see if I can centralize power in MV
and I'm going to use the lazurite to get some good sodium batteries
think I'm going to dig a lot of lazurite
use it for the aluminum
and use the sodium to make a lot of batteries
which I'm going to try to use to centralize power at MV
centralizing power at MV you still have a little bit of power loss, but
use a annealed cable
you lose basically less than one percent of the energy with every cable block
you can also really make an HV transformer and step up
so you lose like
zero dot two percent of the energy
which I think is totally manageable
but I think that's something I will do in next episode
so I guess for today I can stop here
and see you for the next episode for the MV power centralization
which I think no one ever does
and I will get some fame for that
well, I can do that properly
bye bye
欢迎回来
正如你在我身后看到的
我们现在有很多砖高炉
这确实造成了相当多的污染
这正是为什么我把这些建在离我家很远的地方
嗯，也许有人会说我用那些砖高炉做过头了
但我挺喜欢建造这些的
很多人喜欢做刷怪场来获取钢
但我不喜欢刷怪场、魔法之类的东西
我想玩一个工业游戏、科技游戏
而砖高炉就是我们玩工业科技游戏的方式
但我的意思是，那只是我的看法
我甚至让它们挂机运行了很久
所以现在我有这么多钢可以用
钢太多了
顺便说一下，进入污染这么严重的区域会给你带来不少负面效果
如果你不想处理这个
有一个任务可以交换一些
这里有一个任务可以用一些胶水换一套防化服
一些橡胶
给任务书提交一些橡胶
它就会给你一套防化服
那件护甲会保护你免受污染
但它的耐久度非常低
所以你应该只有在去污染区域附近的时候才穿上这件护甲
不管怎样，我们有充足的钢了
我们终于可以开始低压时代的工作了
通常在旧版本中，我会建议用那些配方制作一组马达
因为我们会需要很多马达
一次大量合成
这样你就已经有很多马达了
你就不必担心还要再合成更多
但如今合成马达就是这么简单
我的意思是我不必手动合成这个
手动合成那个
然后手动合成那些
我觉得就是一次合成一个
在需要的时候再合成其实是更好的
因为批量合成只是让你不必手动完成所有这些步骤
但现在NEI一键就能在不到一秒内合成一切
只合成你需要的东西可能更高效
这样你就不会在效率较低的配方上浪费材料
因此我们合成了进入低压时代所需的基本东西
我们或多或少需要所有这些机器
但其中一些比其他的更有用
例如，我的建议是从线材轧机开始
这是最便宜的机器之一
它会大幅提高导线的产量
而不是用三个锭产出两根导线
你会用一个锭产出两根导线
那么现在，是时候连接这些机器了
有些小麻烦你需要检查一下
这根管道只能带得动两个涡轮
但无所谓
你总是可以按自己喜欢的方式来做一点调整
你必须知道它是怎么工作的
这样你才能知道某个东西能不能用
我的意思是说到底
如果某个东西不工作
那就这样吧
我觉得你必须了解的主要事情
如果你经验不够的话
而且这一点经常没有被足够强调的是
这种线缆会有一些能量损耗
这意味着能量每经过一个方块，都会损失一点点
所以尽量把耗能大的机器放在发电机旁边
我以前做过一个视频，更好地解释了它是如何工作的
线材轧机暂时可以放在那里
另一个技巧是，如果你用16号电路板来制作线缆
应该会比用另一个快一点
这个是16x线缆
需要七十秒
所以基本上每根导线一秒
但如果你做普通的导线
两根需要五秒
制作16x线缆大约快两倍
一旦你有了大线缆
你可以
手动拆分成小线缆
做成16x的小尺寸
最后，记住你可以稍微做一点自动化
我不会自动化合成链
特别是现在
特别是有NEI自动合成
但至少在一侧有自动输入、另一侧有自动输出可能会有帮助
这样你就可以把大量材料留给机器处理
机器会把输出留在另一个箱子里
这是你在游戏的这个阶段可能想要的那种自动化
接下来，如果你的机器因为电力不足而停机
你可以用软锤把它关掉再打开
你也可以用红石给机器供能
每块红石值1000 EU
但我不会用它
除非你在某些非常非常非常特殊的情况下
用红石给机器供能不值得
是的，理想情况下你要确保你的涡轮永远不会耗尽燃料
顺便说一下，我用的是蒸汽涡轮
但有很多不同的发电方式
大多数人会尝试使用其他燃料来源
我有我自己独特的玩法
因为我喜欢这样玩
不管怎样，在这个阶段有很多很多很多机器你可能想要
正如我之前所说，你可能想要获取任务书显示的所有东西
你可能想阅读这个时代的每一个任务
其中很多的东西都相当有用
我觉得最有用但可能不是最有用的东西是磁铁
我真的很喜欢有个磁铁，可以在挖掘时轻松捡起所有矿石
我只是觉得不用走来走去捡每一个掉落物真是太好了
顺便说一下，要获取磁铁和锂电池
以及获取锂
我的建议是搞一个多方块蒸汽离心机
这个比低压电动版高效得多
它有一些消耗折扣，还能并行处理
而且你不用处理这些涡轮的低效率问题
你也可以用离心机获取钴或金
要获取金的话，这里我犯了一个错误
如果你想获取金
有多种方法
你可以在NEI中搞清楚
但我建议获取金的方法是粉碎一些铜
然后洗它
关掉磁铁
洗它
你可以在NEI中看到
如果你洗它你会得到钴
如果你用洗矿机你会得到钴
如果你用坩埚你不会得到副产品
研磨机也一样
要获得研磨步骤的副产品
要获得研磨机的那些副产品
你至少需要一台HV研磨机
也就是领先两个等级
所以现在你还不能获得这个副产品，例如
但要轻松获取金
你可以这样处理铜
所以首先你研磨它
然后你在坩埚里洗
我的意思是你可以用普通的洗矿机
但那台机器又一次相当慢而且烦人
有一个蒸汽版的多方块
但我现在不需要那个（副产品？）
所以我就简单地用这种方法
然后你把它扔进离心机
等这粉处理完后应该就能给我们金了
来吧
好的，我就能这样得到金
锂也是一样
你会发现这种矿石相当容易找到和收集
把含杂粉离心，你就能得到锂
所以要得到这个，你不要洗它
你不洗直接粉碎它
顺便说一下要获取铅
你得做一个简易的传送门生成器才能进入暮色森林
在这里你会发现一条由铅和银组成的矿脉
你可以用它来制作铅青铜
这是最好的管道材料之一
或者至少在这个等级
这是真的真的真的很好的管道材料
但最重要的是
我们可以用银来制作高压太阳能锅炉
这是我最喜欢的发电方式
这些锅炉的主要问题是
每隔一段时间你必须破坏并替换方块，否则你会损失三分之二的蒸汽产量
当你这么做的时候
这些会需要很多水才能填满
所以你最好有一个好的系统来确保它们永远不会缺水
尤其是当你替换方块的时候
大约有二十个这样的太阳能锅炉
我们终于可以给这个时代的主要目标供能了
电高炉
这个多方块带来的主要挑战是如何正确地给它供能
这个多方块运行需要120 EU/t
正如我之前展示的那样
那些线缆有一些损耗
在这种情况下你真的没有多少犯错的余地
所以给出的建议是使用两个能源仓
两个能源仓各接一根线缆
不要把那两个连在一起
然后你把涡轮以直接连接到那些线缆的方式放置
问题是每个能源仓可以接受2安培
而机器本身需要4安培，每tick 30 EU
所以这里你损失了1
经过一个方块就已经变成31了
如果再损失1
你就没有余量了
你基本上是净收益者（？）
所以如果由于某种原因一些电能包丢失了
多方块就会停机
如果你愿意，也可以加第三个能源仓
第三个能源仓会提供未使用的额外能量输入
这可以弥补能量损耗
我不建议在这里使用电池箱
但理论上你可以
但你仍然有个问题，必须确保多方块获得120 EU/t
如果你用两个能源仓
必须让供电非常紧凑
你可以加第三个来弥补损耗
我会尽量减少这里的能量损耗
那么这个时代的一些人会用苯或其他燃料来源
我还在用蒸汽
使用蒸汽
你得小心一点
因为低压蒸汽涡轮需要每秒1552蒸汽才能运转
所以你必须确保你提供了那么多蒸汽
那些是四个
所以我们每秒需要大约七千蒸汽
而普通的铅青铜管道只有六千
所以我不会冒险用这个
我宁愿选大号的
好了
我们给EBF供能了
你还得做维护
你可以制作焊锡和烙铁，这可能就是我要做的
以后吧，但是
现在我很懒
我们去拿胶带
战利品袋没那么好用，我是说
那是一次性物品
所以可能战利品袋更好
但我很懒
就这样吧
顺便说一下
如果出于某种原因你的多方块需要维护了
你会被提示进行维护
好的，这里你可以看到
需要的工具有不同的种类
所以你可以看到第一个是撬棍
第二个应该是软的
软锤和硬锤都可以
螺丝刀、焊锡和扳手
所以你拿着那些工具
然后在维护仓里用那些工具点击
我点击仓，好的
但我们没有，好的
你也可以用这两个东西点击
我之前展示了胶带
现在你可以看到扳手完成了
但最好的办法是搞一个现场工程师工具箱
但那东西需要一些聚乙烯
我本来打算把聚乙烯留到下一集
但你知道吗
让我们看看低压阶段的一些自动化
聚乙烯是一条很长的合成链
我的意思是，如果你了解GTNH的话它其实没那么长
但这是你最可能想做的第一个
有很多种方法可以来做这个
可能会有点迷茫
聚乙烯的任务实际上在MV阶段
但你完全可以在低压阶段做
我其实建议在低压阶段做
硅和聚乙烯两条任务线
那么，要制作它，首先
正如我所说有很多方法
我建议从石油开始
但在我们真正去采油之前
我想我们应该让高炉开始运转
烙铁是最烦人的制作工具
和其他工具一样
你可以用很多不同的方法制作它
我只是选了钢螺栓的版本，但是
你可以用很多不同的东西来制作它
只要用你有的任何电池和螺栓就行
唯一的问题是每种材料有不同的杆
我用的是钢螺栓和铁杆
我已经在没录像的时候做好了
这是一个电动工具
所以你必须给它充电
你可以把它放在机器的任何充电槽里
然后你给它充电
你的物品栏里还需要一些焊锡
它是由锡和锑合金熔炼而成的
然后你只要把它通过线材轧机来制作细导线
一旦你有了所有的工具
你只要点击这个
我想我得把工具移一下
如果你没有工具箱
你必须手动用每个工具点击
来对多方块进行维护
再说一次，你可以这样做，或者之后我们会得到这个
基本上你把每个工具都放进这个东西里
然后你只需使用这个东西
或者就像我之前那样用胶带
现在它可以再次运行了
好的，我们有高炉了
我们可以用这个更快地炼钢
它能在五秒内炼出钢
不像砖版本要六分钟
它消耗相当多的能量
它应该要节能得多
在原始砖高炉中炼钢
你需要四块煤
而这里你需要12000 EU
还有氧气
但问题是，例如这个锅炉用一块煤就能产生近四万蒸汽
四万蒸汽就是两万EU
用这个锅炉一块煤就能做一个半锭
而这里我们需要四块煤
所以，从能量角度来看它更高效
我没有算上能量损耗
但或多或少
这就是为什么，至少
至少也会有三倍以上的效率
而且速度快多了
但我们建造这个的主要原因其实不是为了产钢
而是为了获取铝
为此，我们可以用压缩铝粉花75秒
我现在都不知道怎么弄纯铝粉了
在过去，获取纯铝粉相对容易
但我觉得现在你甚至已经无法获得铝粉了
这个可能行不通
可能在MV阶段
一旦你开始电解，你就能得到这个
正确的方法是将氧化铝和冰晶石混合在一起
冰晶石是一种你可以在暮色森林找到的矿石
而氧化铝可以从几种东西中获得
我不建议，但你可以在暮色森林找到很多蓝宝石
你可以把蓝宝石放进电高炉炼成氧化铝
但那只是一种方法
对于这个等级我要给你的最大建议
这期视频可能是质量最低的之一
我只是跟着任务书走
在这个时代有很多事情你可能想做也可能不想做
我最大的建议就是四处看看
搞清楚你可能喜欢什么
尝试不同的东西
我是想展示给你那些你可能应该记住的主要东西，我知道
但我不觉得光看视频会对你有太大帮助
多自己尝试，自己搞清楚各种事情
记得看每个任务
并记得查看NEI中每一种可能的配方
因为有很多配方
很多做事的方法
大多数配方也支持回收
整合包也在不断更新，不断改变着各种东西
在这个时代我最大的建议是
你会有很长的等待蒸馏或其他事情的时间
所以利用等待时间四处看看
搞清楚你可以做些什么
仅仅是加工冰晶石的铝副产品
我们现在就可以启动EBF了
这会需要一点时间
但每一个新等级我们都会有一种材料需要一点时间来处理
像往常一样，利用这段时间搞清楚你还能做什么
或者只是建造更多那台机器
这次游玩我打算放松一下
所以我就把游戏挂着，直到我们有很多铝
等了一会儿之后
我们得到了足够的铝来做（？）两台MV机器
两台MV机器
电解机
其实还行
用这个
我可以搞一台MV电解机
而MV电解机会让铝的生产容易得多
因为理论上
我们可以电解大量黏土来获得我们可能需要的所有铝
我通常获取铝的主要方法之一是
没错，先到MV，因为那个配方需要MV
蓝金石，这是一种你可以大量获得的矿石
一个矿石能产出十二个
所以你可以得到很多这个
这个能产出大量的硅、钠、铝、钙，都是好东西
但主要的方法，哦等等
他们改了吗，哦，等等
我不建议盲目跟风meta
也不算是主流玩法，但是
哦对，这个
不知道为什么我找不到它
这是一个非常好的配方
如果你找到一个峡谷生物群系
搭一点自动化
在峡谷生物群系中用管道把所有黏土输送到研磨机里
然后电解得到大量的这些东西
钠可以燃烧，等等可以吗？
哦对，你可以在锅炉里燃烧钠
我觉得他们削弱了它
我记得这个烧得更多
但很可能你想把钠用在其他东西上
如果以后你想用电池箱的话，可以用钠制作一些不错的电池
锂非常适合做电池
别烧了它
然后你得到铝
你得到铝
我记得这些配方是用来产出5个铝的
所以，好吧，现在这个方法产铝就是垃圾
这曾经是一种方法
收集所有黏土也需要一点手工劳动
但我觉得现在已经不是这么做的了
我想我得再找另一种获取铝的方法了
不管怎样，你要从EBF获得的另一样东西是为了进MV所需的一些砷化镓
你可以用不同的方式获取砷
再说一次，查看任务书
我是从离心雄黄得到的
但那有点呃
刚好我有雄黄所以我就用了
这是你在下界可以找到的贫瘠矿石
这个在下界以贫瘠矿石的形式生成
只是随机的矿石
当你收集其他材料的时候
你可能会得到一些
你可以离心它
可能就够了
然后对于镓，你用闪锌矿
这里我在这样处理闪锌矿因为我确实需要镓
应该是，让我们看看他们是不是也改了，是的
你电解这个闪锌矿
你有9%的几率获得镓
但如果我们有HV研磨机
我们就能从闪锌矿中得到更多的镓
也有其他方法
闪锌矿也用于我们很后面才会看到的东西
所以，我想说不要处理它，或者说你不需要处理它
因为在将来这种矿石会相当有用
但我也在想，等我们需要它来做那个我们最终会看到的东西的时候
到那时候，我们会有一些巨大的多方块钻井平台
那会给我们带来这么多的这种矿石
我们在这个等级节省的量与那个时代能获取的量相比将毫无意义
另外，我不会给你列清单
当然你不想处理的矿石
那样玩没有任何意义
我有节省那些材料的倾向
因为我已经知道会怎样了
但如果你不知道这些事情
就不要去研究了
在一段太倒霉的过程之后
我们终于得到了镓粉
我们可以把它和2号电路板一起扔进熔炉
来制作砷化镓，完美
任务书想让你用它
研磨它
来制作二极管
但再说一次
任务书建议你用这个配方，让你得到两个二极管……
我觉得是一个砷化镓研磨成小撮粉后能产出16个二极管
但如果你用聚乙烯
你能得到两倍的量
如果你更进一步制作晶圆
这需要硅
你会得到多得多
因为一根单晶硅可以切出16个晶圆
一根单晶硅消耗四分之一的砷化镓
所以如果你改用这个配方的话会高效得多
这也需要聚乙烯和硅，我之前提到过
在我们等待的时候
在我们等待东西的时候
比如你可以直接用更好的配方
多收集一点闪锌矿
从辉钴矿中提取砷
然后就那样做
或者你也可以就做我之前提到的那两套方案
现在，正如我在开始这期视频时多次说过的
通常在低压阶段获取硅和聚乙烯
所以可以这样做
但问题是现在给机器供能
我到处放的都是蒸汽机器
很多人，在我看来太多了
喜欢大量摆放发电机
就像他们甚至加了
他们甚至加了一个IV燃气涡轮
很多人喜欢有一条主燃料管道
用一些能量密度高的流体铺设管道
比如你用柴油或苯
一根超细的管道就能给非常强大的高耗能机器供能
如果你用蒸汽
你需要巨大的管道
但我不喜欢的是有所有那些管道和所有那些发电机
感觉发电机看起来也没那么贵
但我就是不喜欢那种玩法
我宁愿更早地集中供能
通常我在HV阶段集中供能
但这次游玩我想试试能不能在MV阶段集中供能
我打算用蓝金石来搞一些好的钠电池
我觉得我要挖很多蓝金石
用它来产铝
并用钠制作大量电池
我打算用这些来在MV阶段集中供能
在MV阶段集中供能你仍然会有一点能量损耗，但是
使用退火线缆
基本上每个线缆方块损失不到1%的能量
你也可以制作一个HV变压器来升压
这样就只损失
0.2%的能量
我觉得这完全是可以接受的
但我想这是我下一集才会做的事情
所以我想今天我可以到这里了
下一集MV集中供能再见
我觉得从来没有人这样做过
我会因此获得一些名声
好吧，如果我能做好的话
拜拜